<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ana Laura Diedrichs on Ana Laura Diedrichs</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ana Laura Diedrichs on Ana Laura Diedrichs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018-2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT in agriculture </title>
      <link>/talk/2019-sase/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/2019-sase/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicción de heladas con aprendizaje automático e Internet de las cosas </title>
      <link>/talk/2019-latinr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/2019-latinr/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ReLIoT : Reinforcement learning for the Internet of Things.</title>
      <link>/project/reliot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/reliot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SPANISH Description, translation to English in progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;./files/projects/PID-RELIOT-2019_enviado.pdf&#34;&gt;Enlace al PROYECTO presentado&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El aprendizaje por refuerzo es un área de la inteligencia artificial que estudia como un agente (programa, sensor, robot, etc) puede aprender de su entorno a tomar las decisiones sobre las siguientes acciones a ejecutar, basado en una función objetivo
(o varias) modelada a través de un sistema de recompensas y/o penalizaciones. Permite que el agente se desenvuelva en un nuevo entorno y vaya mejorando su desempeño a medida que pasa el tiempo. En el paradigma de Internet de las cosas (IoT)
podemos modificar el comportamiento de los sensores, por ejemplo, indicar cuando las luces irán a encenderse en un hogar o cada cuanto deben medirse y enviarse información ambiental que fue medida en una parcela en el campo. Muchos sistemas de telemetría actualmente requieren bastante intervención humana para ajustar su comportamiento y configuración inicial. En este proyecto proponemos el estudio de técnicas de aprendizaje por refuerzo, área de la inteligencia artificial, aplicadas a IoT para
lograr aplicaciones ?autoconfigurables? en escenarios no críticos. Uno de los limitantes es la escasez de implementaciones o software libre para IoT de algoritmos de aprendizaje por refuerzo. El proyecto propone analizar escenarios de aplicación y ensayar los frameworks o librerías existentes para la construcción de un prototipo de librería de aprendizaje por refuerzo para
IoT. Otro de los objetivos es estudiar y ensayar algoritmos de aprendizaje por refuerzo y proponer mejoras y adaptaciones para su uso en sensores inalámbricos en aplicaciones como edificios inteligentes y/o agricultura de precisión, permitiendo construir sistemas auto-configurables con escasa intervención humana.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SENSE : Smart prEdictioN of froSt and yiEld for the wine industry.</title>
      <link>/project/sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/sense/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The aim of this project is to use environmental &amp;amp; agronomic information to build a dataset for: 1) predicting frost events, 2) Selecting the sensor locations most significative for frost events prediction 3) Understand the impact of temperature, humidity and other environmental factors in the vineyard yield forecasting system. Project description file in Spanish &lt;a href=&#34;./files/projects/PID-5128-Sense-Diedrichs-20190222.pdf&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>frost: an R package - prediction of minimum temperature for frost forecasting in agriculture </title>
      <link>/talk/2018-latinr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/2018-latinr/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethics concerns in IoT and AI</title>
      <link>/talk/2018-ietfday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/2018-ietfday/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internet &amp; the future. Artificial Intelligence and the work industry future</title>
      <link>/talk/2018-argensig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/2018-argensig/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prediction of frost events using machine learning and IoT sensing devices</title>
      <link>/publication/ieeeiot2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/ieeeiot2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prediction of frost using machine learning</title>
      <link>/project/frost-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/frost-prediction/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIPIA: Sensores inalámbricos para la Investigación Agronómica</title>
      <link>/project/sipia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/sipia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Farmers can lose everything in a couple of hours In 2013, 85% of the peach production in the Mendoza region (Argentina) was lost because of frost. Because less fruit was produced in the region, 600.000 less work days were needed to process the harvest between November 2013 and March 2014, a reduction in work force of 10.600 people. Across the Mendoza region, frost has caused a loss of revenue of 950 million Argentine pesos roughly 100 million USD in the peach business alone.
TO BE COMPLETED&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save the peaches</title>
      <link>/project/save-the-peaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/save-the-peaches/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Farmers can lose everything in a couple of hours In 2013, 85% of the peach production in the Mendoza region (Argentina) was lost because of frost. Because less fruit was produced in the region, 600.000 less work days were needed to process the harvest between November 2013 and March 2014, a reduction in work force of 10.600 people. Across the Mendoza region, frost has caused a loss of revenue of 950 million Argentine pesos roughly 100 million USD in the peach business alone.
A frost event happens when the temperature is so low that the crops cannot recover their tissue or internal structure from the effects of water freezing inside or outside the plant. For the peach production, a critical period is when the trees are in bloom and fruit set (Aug./Sept. in Mendoza), during which the temperature needs to be kept above 3° C. Even a few hours below that temperature causes flowers to fall, preventing fruits to grow.
The goal of the project is to predict frost events in peach orchards by using dense monitoring using low-power wireless mesh networking technology. Off-the-shelf commercial solutions are available today which offer &amp;gt;99.999% end-to-end data reliability and a decade of battery lifetime. We deploy low-power wireless mesh networks of temperature, relative humidity and soil moisture sensors directly into the orchard. We use machine learning and pattern recognition to build a micro-climate predictive model by continuously analyzing the gathered sensor data in real time, and issue early frost warnings.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using SmartMesh IP in Smart Agriculture and Smart Building Applications</title>
      <link>/publication/comcom2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/comcom2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>frost: An R package</title>
      <link>/project/frost-r-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/frost-r-package/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The version 0.0.4 of the frost package is published on &lt;a href=&#34;https://cran.r-project.org/web/packages/frost/index.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CRAN&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/anadiedrichs/frost&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;frost package GitHub repository&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Not so) intuitive results from a smart agriculture low-power wireless mesh deployment</title>
      <link>/publication/not-so-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/not-so-results/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A demo of the PEACH IoT-based frost event prediction system for precision agriculture</title>
      <link>/publication/demo-peach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/demo-peach/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
