<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Ana Laura Diedrichs</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Ana Laura Diedrichs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018-2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ReLIoT : Reinforcement learning for the Internet of Things.</title>
      <link>/project/reliot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/reliot/</guid>
      <description>SPANISH Description, translation to English in progress.
Enlace al PROYECTO presentado
El aprendizaje por refuerzo es un área de la inteligencia artificial que estudia como un agente (programa, sensor, robot, etc) puede aprender de su entorno a tomar las decisiones sobre las siguientes acciones a ejecutar, basado en una función objetivo (o varias) modelada a través de un sistema de recompensas y/o penalizaciones. Permite que el agente se desenvuelva en un nuevo entorno y vaya mejorando su desempeño a medida que pasa el tiempo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SENSE : Smart prEdictioN of froSt and yiEld for the wine industry.</title>
      <link>/project/sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/sense/</guid>
      <description>The aim of this project is to use environmental &amp;amp; agronomic information to build a dataset for: 1) predicting frost events, 2) Selecting the sensor locations most significative for frost events prediction 3) Understand the impact of temperature, humidity and other environmental factors in the vineyard yield forecasting system. Project description file in Spanish here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prediction of frost using machine learning</title>
      <link>/project/frost-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/frost-prediction/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIPIA: Sensores inalámbricos para la Investigación Agronómica</title>
      <link>/project/sipia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/sipia/</guid>
      <description>Farmers can lose everything in a couple of hours In 2013, 85% of the peach production in the Mendoza region (Argentina) was lost because of frost. Because less fruit was produced in the region, 600.000 less work days were needed to process the harvest between November 2013 and March 2014, a reduction in work force of 10.600 people. Across the Mendoza region, frost has caused a loss of revenue of 950 million Argentine pesos roughly 100 million USD in the peach business alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save the peaches</title>
      <link>/project/save-the-peaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/save-the-peaches/</guid>
      <description>Farmers can lose everything in a couple of hours In 2013, 85% of the peach production in the Mendoza region (Argentina) was lost because of frost. Because less fruit was produced in the region, 600.000 less work days were needed to process the harvest between November 2013 and March 2014, a reduction in work force of 10.600 people. Across the Mendoza region, frost has caused a loss of revenue of 950 million Argentine pesos roughly 100 million USD in the peach business alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>frost: An R package</title>
      <link>/project/frost-r-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/frost-r-package/</guid>
      <description>The version 0.0.4 of the frost package is published on CRAN.
frost package GitHub repository</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>